* 穿过广阔的红木林
* From the redwood forests
* 跨域蜿蜒的河流
* to the gulf stream waters
* 这片热土属于你和我
* this land w made for you and me
绿色的 清洁的
THE ONLY CLEAN IS GREEN
大自然会如何反击
WHAT WOULD NATURE DO?
你们的目的已经达到了abc能让我们复工了吗?
You made your point. Now howabc'bout letting us do our jobs?
除非你们公司不再滥伐森林abc我们的行动才算有成效
Our point'll be made when your companyabcstops tearing down this mountain.
那谁来养活我们的娃? 你?
Then who's gonna feed our kids? You?
如果你爱你的孩子abc你会希望他们长大后还能呼吸新鲜空气
If you really cared about your kids,you'd want them to have air to breathe when they grow up.
你说啥 你这个狗娘养的?
What'd you say,you son of a bitch?
你们不是罪魁祸首
You guys aren't the problem.
你们是最大受害者
You're being hurt more than anyone.
你们吸入大量煤粉
You breathe in that coal dust.
煤碳是世界上污染最严重的能源
Coal is the dirtiest energy on earth.
请求增派支援
Gonna need some backup.
你们这些混蛋对环境的伤害还不够深吗?
Not enough for you thugs toabcassault the environment?
Doug 拜托 别说了
Doug,please,don't.
Susan? Susan! 没事吧?
Susan? Susan! You okay?
她必须入院治疗
She needs to get to a hospital.
她脱水而已 我们有药
She's just dehydrated.abcWe have medics here.
- 给她喝些水abc- 她脉搏都没了
- Let 'em give her fluids.abc- She has no pulse.
你若不松开手 我就要动手了
Either unhook your arm,orabcI'm gonna break it off.
无论如何 这次抗议到此为止
Either way,this protest is over.
抗议结束了
protest is over**
好吧
All right.
- 我怎么了?abc- 你晕倒了
- What happened?abc- You passed out.
没事 只是有点脱水
It's okay. Just stay hydrated.
我们不会就此罢休 我们还会回来的!
You know we'll be back. We'll be back!
嘿 别胡闹了
Hey,stop screwing around.
我没有胡闹 我只是...
I'm not... screwingabcaround. I just can't...
我站不住了
I can't stand up.
我们得推迟度假
I need to push back our getaway.
千万不要啊 我刚帮你找到冲浪板abc最适合初学者
No,you don't. Found you aabcboard. Perfect size to learn on.
只是迟点去度假而已
I'm just postponing.
费城综合医院的Olandtabc有个病人想让House诊断
Olandt from philly general wantsabcme to get a patient in to see house.
然后呢?
So?
我欠他人情
I owe him a favor.
去年我转诊了许多病人到他那儿
He's taken about a dozen of myabcreferrals over the last year.
那得花上你5秒钟把病历交给House
I meant so  that's fiveabcseconds to hand house the file,
30分钟让他揣测你的真实意图
30 for him to questionabcyour real motives,
1分钟就是聆听abc他对你和13美腿的无聊比较...
a minute for witty comments comparingabcthe length of your legs to thirteen's...
时间绰绰有余让你去海滩度假啊
plenty of time left over for the shore.
我得确定我不在时他不会扔了那病历
I need to make sure he doesn't toss the fileabcin the trash as soon as I'm out of sight.
亲爱的 你这人情就不能迟点还吗?
Baby,can't repay theabcfavor on another case?
经历了上周 我真的需要离开这里透透气
After last week,I could reallyabcuse a break from this place.
我们都得歇歇
We both could.
一知道他真的接收了这个病例abc我们立即出发
Once I'm sure he's really onabcthe case,then we're out of here.
然后我的腿和其他的都归你了
And these legs and every otherabcpart of me will be all yours.
他看了3个专科医生
He's seen three different specialists.
挺好玩的
Interesting.
同样有趣的是 你在Kutner离开我们不久
Almost as interesting as you tryingabcto step into kutner's shoes just days
就急于取代他
after he stepped out of them.
我不是想取代他
I am not shoe shopping.
我只是想还个人情给那个转诊的医生
I'm just trying to repay aabcfavor to his referring doctor.
这病例很难吗?
What's the mystery?
这个呆子整天在有毒废弃物堆积场抗议
The nut case spends all his free timeabcwreaking havoc at toxic waste dumps.
毒理分析无异常
Tox screen's negative.
神经系统 肌肉及心血管均未见异常
No neurological,muscular,orabccardiovascular abnormalities.
这家伙热衷保护地球环境?abc那这是个疯子
The guys cares about the environment?abcThat makes him a nut case?
他是个20多岁的单身男性
He's a single guy in his 20s.
他想泡的那个美眉abc恰巧是环保分子罢了
He cares about getting his hybrid waxedabcgirls who care about the environment.
看到没? 才不是呆子
See? Not a nut case.
他可能只是装病 为了向警察提出诉讼abc获得六位数的赔偿
He's probably just faking so he can sueabcthe cops and get a six-figure settlement.
如果他是诈病
If he was trying to fake an illness,
为什么他还要找全国最棒的abc鉴别诊断医生呢?
why would he consent to be seen byabcthe best diagnostician in the country?
现在是谁在献殷勤?
Now who's trying toabcget her hybrid waxed?
去做个前庭冷热试验吧
We need to do a vestibular caloric test.
看看平衡的问题abc是来源于脖子上部还是下部
See if the balance problemabcstarts above or below the neck.
我说的我们 其实是指你
And when I say "we," I mean "you."
是你要还人情 不是他们
You're the one with theabcfavor to repay,not them.
我要往你耳朵注入冷水
I'm going to be injectingabcice water in your ear canal.
如果引起不同方向的眼球震颤abc那么就是内耳的问题
If the resulting eye movements are at allabcerratic,then the balance problem is in your inner ear.
每个病房都有鲜花?
Those in every room?
应该是吧
I think so.
能把花拿走吗?
Can you get rid of them?
最好把所有房间的花都拿走abc可以吗?
Preferably from every room?
为了种植商品花卉abc他们用了不下于30种杀虫剂
They use over 30 pesticidesabcto grow commercial flowers.
没有这些 医药行业会更...
You'd think the medicalabcindustry would be a lot more...
你担心医药行业? 先把身体养好
concerned with medicine?abcLet's fix your body.
那样你才能回去继续保护地球
Then you can go backabcto fixing the earth.
这会有点不适
This is gonna get aabclittle uncomfortable.
我整整铁链缠身14小时
I just spent 14 hours chained to a tire.
很多医生建议--
Most doctorsabcwould recommend--
我们的地球正面临毁灭
Our planet's headed for destruction.
海水即将淹没海岸abc数百万种生物濒临灭绝
Coastlines under water,aabcmillion species extinct.
我觉得好像整个人在旋转
Feels like I'm tumbling head over heels.
正常的--这试验有时候会引起眩晕
That's normal--sometimesabcthis test causes vertigo.
还有恶心呕吐
And nausea.
Cameron给了我一个病例
Cameron just brought me a case.
Cameron在急诊干得很开心
Cameron is happy in the E.R.
她绝对不会想重回你的魔爪
There's no way she wants herabcnose back on your grindstone.
煎蛋卷 不要培根 全麦吐司
Egg white omelet,noabcbacon,whole wheat toast.
我不是说她钟意我的魔爪 她另有所图
I say it's not my grindstone she'sabcafter and not her nose she wants on it.
她和Chase同居了
She and chase areabcpractically living together.
你刚刚点了啥?
What did you just order?
煎蛋卷
An omelet.
你啥时候起不爱吃猪肉了?
Since when do you pass on the swine?
全麦面包? 可能味道和砂纸一样哦
And wheat toast? Might asabcwell eat a sheet of sand paper.
没错 我不想要两天吃相同的东西
Well,yes,but I don't like eatingabcthe same thing two days in a row.
弟弟的护士不喜欢你的肉肉?
Your bro's nurse notabclovin' the love handles?
我只是不想再吃培根而已
I'm just not in the mood for bacon.
而奇怪的是你明显不想谈论Kutner的事
And you're obviously trying to avoidabctalking about kutner,which is odd,
因为你有一周时间都在追查他为什么--
because you spent a wholeabcweek obsessing about why--
他不再是我的团队的一员
He's no longer on my team.
很遗憾他不再是我们的一员abc仅此而已
I'm sorry he's no longer on myabcteam. Nothing else to talk about.
你带着的表是他送的圣诞礼物
You're wearing the watch heabcgave you for secret santa.
它有大功能 包括秒表abc可以用来算算你关怀我的时间哦
Five functions,including a stop watch to timeabchow long it takes you to ask me if I'm okay.
你要什么?
You gonna order?
我不饿了
Not hungry.
奇怪 虽然她以前也把病人转给我们abc但他从来不会让她去做检查
It's just weird. She's brought casesabcbefore,but he's never made her run the tests.
发生了这些事abc他可能只是想要些安慰
Maybe he's looking for someone toabcmother him after what happened.
长鞭 皮尿布还有信用卡abc才是House想要的安抚
Only kind of mothering house wants involvesabca bullwhip,leather diapers,and a credit card.
妈妈回来了哦
Mommy's home.
检查让患者吐到不用吃午餐abc但冷热试验是正常的 内耳没事
Test made the patient lose his lunch,but hisabccalorics are normal,his inner ear is fine,
而他还是无法保持平衡
and he still can't balance himself.
还要多少正常的检查结果abc才能证明他在诈病呢?
How many normal test resul do we need toabcknow the patient's a granola-filled phony?
他没有诈病
He's not lying about his symptoms.
- 你知道是因为...abc- 她换了鞋
- And you know this because...abc- She changed her shoes.
如果他诈病abc就会朝着床的另一边呕吐
If he was faking,he'd haveabcvomited on the other side of the bed.
和警察冲突及把自己锁起数日abc都会导致应激
Sparring with the police and chainingabcyourself up for days can cause stress.
应激会影响心血管系统
Stress screws with theabcheart and arteries.
动脉粥样硬化会引起失衡
Carotid atherosclerosis couldabccause a loss of balance.
CT和MRI结果都无异常
Wouldn't show upon ct or mri.
可能是中风前的唯一预警
Could also be our only warningabcbefore a massive stroke.
做个动态心电图和心脏彩超
Do a holter and a carotid doppler.
看看他的心脏会不会有斑林鸮一样的斑块
See if his heart skips forabcmore than the spotted owl.
尽管我没说我们 即使说了 也...
Although I didn't say "we." If I had...
希望这不会影响检查结果
Sorry if this is screwing up the test.
我最近经常打嗝 但...
I've been hiccupping a lot lately,but...
没有像现在这么严重
Not as bad as this.
"经常"及"最近"具体指的是什么?
How much is "a lot" andabchow long is "lately"?
反复发作一周了
It's been on and off for about a week.
每天持续数小时
Maybe a few hours a day.
有没有把这告诉费城医院的医生?
Did you tell theabcdoctors in philly about it?
他们似乎不把这当回事
They didn't seem toabcthink it was any big deal.
嘿 我们还是明天出发 对吗?
Hey,so we're stillabcleaving tomorrow,aren't we?
我也不太肯定
I'M not sure.
转诊医生没有重视他的呃逆--
The referring doctors didn't realizeabcthat his hiccups were--
呃逆?
Hiccups?
根据发作的时间及频率abc很可能是病理性的 可能挺严重的
With this durationand intensity,mostly likelyabcpathological,and it could mean it's serious.
- 你在避开我吗?abc- 没有啊
- Are you avoiding me?abc- No.
让人疑惑的是你宁愿治疗转诊的呃逆患者
So I shouldn't beat all concerned that you'reabctreating another doctor's patient for hiccups
也不愿和我去旅行abc我可是计划了一周
instead of going on aabcvacationI spent a week planning.
在这病例上花较多时间是有原因的
There is a reason I need to stayabcwith this case a while longer,
但我不能告诉你
but I can't tell you what it is.
所以你承认你骗了我abc还要求我信任你咯?
So... you admit you lied to me. Andabcnow you're asking me to trust you?
没错
Yes.
好吧
Okay.
心脏和血管都没问题abc但他时不时打嗝已一星期了
No sign of heart or arterial problems,but he'sabcbeen hiccupping on and off for over a week.
好极! 我被迷住了
Nice! I'm hooked.
你可以回急诊室当班了
You can get back toabcyour shift at the E.R.
但据急诊室所知abc你正在放假 不是吗?
Except,as far as the E.R.Isabcconcerned,you're on vacation,right?
我把旅行延后了abc因为我关心这病人
I postponed a trip because I'mabcconcerned about the patient.
这只能解释你为什么放Chase鸽子abc并参与鉴别诊断 解释不了你答应做测试
Explains why you ditched chase and came toabcthe differentials,not why you ran the tests.
你让我做的
You told me to.
但我不是你上司abc你不是一向很乐于指出这点吗?
Well,I'm not your boss,as you usuallyabctake great pleasure in pointing out.
嘿 你该不会还在迷恋我吧?
Hey,you don't stillabchave the hots for me,do you?
我关心这个病人abc关心你医疗小组的同事
I care about the patient,and I careabcabout the people who work on your team.
他们最近经历了很多abc我只是想 我--
They've been through a lotabclately. I just thought I--
是佛罗伦斯-南丁格尔
Was florence nightingale.
你要照顾我们 直至我们元神归位
Yeah,you're gonna nurse us back toabcspiritual and mental oneness.
这番对话发生在一星期前才有意义
That would make sense if we were havingabcthis conversation a week ago.
我知道你在想什么--abc你以为我想回来工作
Think what you want--abcthat I'm here to get a job,
以为我把你当小宝宝哄着
that I'm here to wrapabcyou in swaddling clothes.
问题是 我没这么想abc因为两者都说不通
The problem is,I think neither.abcBecause neither makes sense.
唯一说得通的是...没有
The only thing that does... doesn't.
病理性呃逆加上无法保持平衡-- 开始
Pathological hiccups plusabcinability tbalance--go.
照她说的做
What she said.
脑子可以联系两者
Brain would connect the two.
有可能 假如Cameron还没abc给他做头部CT的话
It could,if cameronabchadn't already ct'd his head.
和她男友的日程表一样空虚
Empty as her boyfriend's calendar.
这和Chase有什么关系?
What does this have to do with chase?
- 没有abc- 现在说不准
- Nothing.abc- Not sure yet.
病人正在发动一场abc讨伐商品花卉的圣战
Patient is on a jihad againstabccommercial flowers.
他曾在多家花圃抗议abc有机磷酸酯类中毒会引起打嗝和--
He's picketed several nurseries. Organophosphateabcpoisoning can cause both hiccups and--
没有肠胃问题 没有唾沫分泌过多
No G.I. Problems,no hyper-salivation.
可能和他的抵抗行动无关
It's possible it's notabcconnected to a protest.
CT查不出多发性硬化症abc他姓Swenson
M.S.Wouldn't show on theabcct,and his name's swenson.
斯堪的纳维亚人的后裔abc更易患上多发性硬化症
Scandinavians have anabcincreased susceptibility to M.S.
这理论比说他装病强
Better theory than he's faking it.
北欧木屐汉的推测胜出abc做脊髓穿刺确认多发性硬化症
The clogs have it. Do aabclumbar puncture to confirm M.S.
我们继续坐一边绕大拇指好了
I guess we'll justabccontinue to twiddle our thumbs.
真希望你这话另有所指
God,I hope that's a euphemism.
病人不停呃逆 我怎么做脊髓穿刺?
How am I supposed to do a lumbar punctureabcon a patient with intractable hiccups?
我在想你这句话在暗指什么
I'm trying to figure outabcwhat that could be a euphemism for.
自个儿想办法去
You'll find a way.
你帮我做检查 不怕House迁怒于你?
You're not worried house is gonna beabcpissed you're helping me do the test?
他让你想办法 这不就是了
He said find a way,and you did.
House最近怎么样?
How do you think house is doing?
- 你是为这个而来?abc- 是的
- That why you're here?abc- Yeah.
不 你不是
No,it isn't.
虽然Kutner的死使House深受打击abc但这对他不是问题
Even if house was messed up byabckutner's suicide,it wouldn't matter.
他向来认为生命是一个abc肮脏 残酷 漫长的过程
He already thinks life isabcnasty,brutish,and long.
痛苦反而有助他的诊断
And misery helps his diagnostic skills.
你很清楚这一点 那么...
All of which you know,so...
- 你究竟是为了什么?abc- 我怎么回答你才会相信?
- why are you here?abc- Which answer would you believe?
如果你想顶替Kutner的位置abc我没有意见
If you want kutner'sabcplace,it's fine by me.
权当多一个有胆色的帮手abc和我一同对抗House
I could use someone else with theabcstones to stand up to house.
但你必须知道 这会毁了你和Chase的关系
But you've gotta know it's gonnaabcblow up your relationship with chase.
我只不过推迟了一个三天的旅行
All I did was postpone a three-day trip.
离开Chase 来到House身边
With chase,to be with house.
- 你要干什么?abc- 去拿静脉注射的氯丙嗪
- What are you doing?abc- Ordering I.V.Chlorpromazine.
可能是神经性问题导致abc这么做会使其精神状况恶化
This could still be neurological.abcYou could cloud his mental status.
你想把针扎准 还是光说不练?
You wanna get the needle inabchis spine or you wanna talk?
你和House谈过填补Kutner空缺没?
You and house been talking aboutabcfilling kutner's slot?
是的 我们刚参加完葬礼 就去了人力资源部
Yeah,we went straight from theabcfuneral to human resources.
你想回去他的医疗小组?
You interested inabcgetting back on the team?
我只想知道Cameron有没这意思
I'm interested in knowing ifabccameron's interested.
她正为House的病人做检查
She's been running allabcthe tests for house's case.
她什么也没和我说
Well,she hasn't said anything to me.
我猜 大概是转介病人的医生abc让她多关注些
But I guess,uh,the referring doctorabcmight have asked her to keep an eye on him.
你觉得Cameron爱House吗?
Do you think cameron's inabclove with house?
这是个荒唐的问题 她爱的是你
That is a ridiculous question.abcShe's in love with you.
那你爱House吗?
Are you in love with house?
这...个问题更荒唐
That... is an evenabcmore ridiculous question.
两个问题 都没有答案
Two questions,zero answers.
我可以从中得出结论了
Think I can extrapolate from there.
House医生?
Dr. House?
抱歉 我是送外卖的
Sorry,I'm st the zone delivery guy.
我是Doug Swenson的妻子
I'm,uh,doug swenson's wife.
病历显示 这位环保神风斗士未婚
His history said theabcenvironmental kamikaze was single.
他也许不想我担心
He,um,he probablyabcdidn't want me to worry.
他告诉我 他和别的抗议者abc一起被关进监狱了
He told me he was in jailabcwith some of the other protesters.
没错 那儿让人放心多了
Yeah,no worries there.
他...经常进监狱
He'S... in jail a lot.
医院倒是很少上
Not so often in the hospital.
我查了他的电邮abc发现他昨天被转介到你这了
I searched his email,and I foundabcthe referral to you yesterday.
你一定很爱你丈夫abc而且出行坐的是黄包车
You must really love yourabchusband. Antravel by rickshaw.
只花18小时就赶到这儿了
It only took you 18 hours to get here.
怎么会有人吃羽衣甘蓝?
Who eats kale?
淡而无味 吃起来abc连羽衣甘蓝都不像
It's so bland,it doesn'tabceven taste like kale.
我得先找人照顾我们四岁大的儿子
Uh,I had to find somebody toabctake care of our four-year-old son.
- Doug没事吧?abc- 我不知道
- Doug's all right,isn't he?abc- I have no idea.
我只知道他是个白痴abc现在加上一条 还是个骗子
I know he's an idiot. And nowabcI've learned that he's a liar.
所以我们--abc谁告诉你我在这儿的?
So we're making a-- whoabctold you that I was in here?
你隔壁办公室的医生说abc你可能会在这
The doctor in the office next toabcyours said that you might be here.
我找到原因了
I got it figured out.
那么不用做脊髓穿刺了?
That mean we don't need to do the lp?
我在和她说话abc你根本不应该出现在这
I was talking to her. You'reabcnot even supposed to be here.
- 你想我们停下还是继续?abc- 什么?
- You want us to stop or not?abc- What?
我才不管你们怎么折腾他
Oh,I don't care what you do with him.
你不是卖费城的医生人情
You're not doing aabcfavor for a doctor in philly.
而是为了帮北新泽西一个肿瘤医生的忙
You're doing a favor for anabconcologist in north jersey.
我在替Wilson监视你?
I'm spying on you for wilson?
监视 悲伤辅导的前期手段
Spying,preemptive grief counseling.
Wilson见你的机会比我多10倍abc而且骗人的手法更高明
Wilson sees you ten times moreabcthan I do,he's a better liar,
而且他不必取消假期来干这个
and he wouldn't have toabccancel a vacation to do it.
说的也是
Good points.
但还是解释不了他为什么变换食谱
Also doesn't explain the diet.
这和我丈夫有什么关系?
What does any of this haveabcto do with my husband?
没关系
Nothing.
来见见环保狂人太太
Meet mrs. Environmental nut bag.
或者你用的是原来的姓氏?
Or did you keep your maiden name?
- 他结婚了?abc- 是的 孩子都生了
- He's married?abc- Yep,got a kid too.
双重威胁 既是环保怪胎abc又是不负责任的老爸
Double threat. Eco-freakabcand dead beat dad.
- Houseabc- 抱歉...为人父母挑战多
- House.abc- Sorry... parentally challenged.
不 是他的脖子
No,his neck.
出现斜颈 是对氯丙嗪的反应
It's torticollis. Reactionabcto the chlorpromazine.
不只是痉挛 还出现肿胀
It's not just a spasm. It's swollen.
嘎吱声
Crunchy.
肯定不是多发性硬化症
It's definitely not M.S.
碎裂的声音是肺部漏气引起的
Crunching sounds were causedabcbyan air leak between his lungs.
持续呃逆可使空气进入胸腔纵隔
Lead in his mediastinum could haveabcbeen caused by prolonged hiccups.
更有可能的是 这只是脖子痉挛
More likely,it was the neck spasm.
最有可能的是abc这问题一直存在
Most likely,it was there all along.
只是我们没有发现abc直至其它症状使之恶化
We just didn't notice it tillabcthe other symptoms made it worse.
那么...是什么导致他失去平衡abc病理性呃逆以及他的肺部穿孔
So... what causes loss of balance,pathologicalabchiccups,and a hole in his gloria steinem?
他去年秋天参加了抵抗木材厂的运动abc肉瘤可能是松林引起的
He was protesting a lumber mill last fall.abcSarcoid's been linked to pine forests.
不 他的血清ACE水平正常
No,his A.C.E. Levels were normal.
进行性系统性硬化症?
Progressive systemic sclerosis?
这家伙成天呆在工业废料区
Guy practically lives atabcindustrial waste sites.
废弃物质被他吸入肺部abc引起自体免疫疾病大爆发...
If a solvent got absorbed through hisabclungs,caused an autoimmune firestorm...
给他静脉注射甲基脱氢皮质醇abc治疗系统性硬化症
Start him on iv methyl-prednisoloneabcfor stemic sclerosis.
做一个全面的检查确认
Do a full work-up to confirm.
- 我一个人?abc- 不用你了
- By myself?abc- Without yourself.
拿起球棒上场 你下场歇着吧abc该换第一阵容出战了
Grab a bat. Grab some pine.abcTime to bring in the first string.
为什么?
Why?
显然你想呆在这里abc我也不知道为什么
You obviously want to beabchere. I can't figure out why.
但我倒想看看abc不让你呆这 你会去哪
I wanna see where youabcgo when you can't be here.
你知道假期是什么意思吗?
You know what vacation means,right?
你找我 是因为House Chaseabc还是超时加班?
You're here because ofabchouse,chase,or overtime issues.
他很担心你
He's very concerned.
我指Chase 不是House
Chase,not... house.
如果你不介意的话 这问题abc我想和Chase私下讨论解决
Well,if it'sall right with you,I'd rather communicateabcwith chase by communicating with chase.
你爱House吗?
Are you in love with house?
你...不是关心我
You... are not concerned about me.
你在圈定你的领地
You're marking your territory.
你不应该和House纠缠
You shouldn't be involved with house.
我也是 任何人都不应该这么做
Neither should I. Neither should anyone.
你和Chase一起很幸福abc不要毁了这一切
You and chase are good together.abcJust don't screw it up.
你什么时候才会收手?
When are you gonna stop this?
你怎么可以让我收手?
How can you ask me to stop?
你都进医院了 我们还有个儿子
You're in a hospital. You have a son.
类固醇应该可以让他的呼吸恢复正常
The steroids ought to getabchim breathing normally again.
但他的自体免疫疾病很严重
But autoimmune diseases are serious.
在家多休息 把身体养好abc也许不是个坏主意
It might not be a bad idea toabctake some time at home,rest up.
我不能退出
I can't just quit.
你真的这么讨厌我们?
Do you hate us that much?
我爱你 也爱我们的儿子
I love you. And I love our son.
但凭什么他就比别人重要?
But why should he matterabcmore than everyone else's?
- 他当然重要abc- 为什么?
- He does.abc- Why?
因为他和我有血缘关系?
Because he'sabcbiologically connected to me?
根本没有合理的解释
There's no rational reason.
他是我们的儿子!
He's our son!
他需要喝到清洁的水源
And he's gonna need to drink clean water.
呼吸清新的空气
And breathe clean air.
我这么做也是为了他
I'm doing this for him too.
进来吧 House
Come on in,house.
除了你 晚上10:30还会有谁呢?
Because who else is it goingabcto be at 10:30 at night?
还有 不必 谢了 我吃过了
And no,thanks. I already ate.
不是来找你吃饭的
Didn't ask you to dinner.
你本来有此打算
But you were going to.
当我解释道 我老早就吃过了
And when I explained thatabcI'd eaten hours ago,
你就会径直步向目标abc大肆搜查我的厨房
you were going to move onto your realabcentree,rifling through my kitchen.
主动邀我搜索厨房
inviting me to search your kitchen.
意味着 你知道我什么也找不到abc或者知道我会找到什么
Means you know that I'd find nothing,orabcyou know that I'd find something,
你指望我以为是前者 从而放弃搜索
so you're hoping that I'm going to assumeabcthe former and I won't bother to look.
或者意味着时候不早 我困了
Or it means it's late,I'm tired,
我就知道 一个煎蛋卷abc都能让你演绎出一番谬论
I know you're here to advance some paranoidabctheory based on a single egg white omelet,
我只想赶紧打发你 好上床睡觉
and I'd like to get it overabcwith so we can both go to sleep.
你的蛋卷论忽略了abc你今天草屯子般的午餐食谱:
Your single-omelet theory convenientlyabcoverlooks the grassy knoll you had for lunch today:
蔬菜和谷物大杂烩
Vegetable and graingag-athon.
华伦委员会没能找到第二份午餐的证据abc(调查肯尼迪遇刺事件)
The warren commission found noabcevidence of a second lunch,possibly
因为它被人从医生休息室里偷走了
because it was stolen fromabcthe doctor's lounge.
你没有变胖
You're not getting any fatter.
医疗纪录也没问题
Your medical records were clean.
- 你查了我的--abc- 你今晚一个人呆着 说明这是因为Kutner
- You checked my-- - You'reabcalone tonight,so it's kutner.
Kutner和这个有什么--
How could kutner haveabcany conceivable--
你的病人有的救活了 有的死去了
Your patients live,your patients die.
你学会了置身事外 淡然处之
You float above itabcall like a medical colossus.
- 但一个同事的离去...abc- 你太厉害了
- But a fellow doctor dies...abc- That's brilliant.
Kutner的死简直是当头棒喝abc提醒我饮食不当好比慢性自杀
Kutner was a wake-up call that if Iabcdidn't eat healthier,I might kill myself.
死亡的杀伤力惊人
Mortality is mortality.
雪糕...也摆在那里
And... ice cream... is ice cream.
有全脂的
Full fat content.
四倍脂的
Quadruple fat content.
没有拆包证明你没有吃
Tuff you haven't eatenabcjust proves you haven't eaten it.
你要我吃过的证据?
You were hoping forabcevidence of stuff I have eaten?
右边第一扇门
First door on the right.
他的左腿10分钟前开始剧烈疼痛!
Excruciating pain in his left leg!abcAcute onset about ten minutes ago.
你们在对他干什么?
What are you doing to him?
我猜他们在找血管搏动
I assume they were checking forabcvascular pulsations.
要么他们找不到abc要么他是个怕疼鬼
Either it's negative,or he's a big wuss.
不是肿瘤或动脉瘤!
It's not a tumor or an aneurism!
- 代谢性骨病?abc- 骨密度正常!
- Metabolic bone disease?abc- Bone density's normal!
但上面的覆盖物未必!
But the bone covering might not be!
如果是骨髓炎 感染侵蚀他的骨膜--
If it's osteomyelitis,an infectionabceang away at his periosteum--
能解释疼痛
That explains the pain.
可能是类固醇导致亚临床感染更严重
Odds are it's a subclinical infection that weabcmade it worse with the steroids we gave him.
静脉注射抗生素 腿照X片确认骨髓炎
Start him on iv antibiotics. X-rayabchis legs to confirm osteomyelitis.
Cameron已经作过下肢X线检查了
Cameron's already donea fullabcset of lower-body x-rays.
感染明显恶化了 再做一次
The infection obviouslyabcflared. Do 'em again.
就算我改了食谱abc又为什么不让你知道呢?
Even if I had changed my diet,what possibleabcreason couldI have for hiding it from you?
踝关节 胫骨 腓骨--都正常
Ankle,tibia,fibula--allabclook normal.
无炎症 无骨髓炎
No inflammation,no signs of osteo.
坚持一下 快完了
Hang in there. We're almost done.
你和你妻子...平时交流吗?
You and your wife...abcyou talk about stuff?
- 性abc- 不是
- Sex.abc- No.
- 还有呢?abc- 钱
- Anything else?abc- Money.
我鼓起勇气问问
I'm gonna go way out on a limb here.
Foreman不爱说话?
Foreman not a chatty cathy?
通常来说没关系
Normally,it doesn't matter.
但上周他这样让我不安
But last week it did.
你和男人约会 很可能得适应...
You wanna date men,goodabcchance talking won't be...
他的大腿骨骨折
his femur's fractured.
不可能 那可是全身最坚硬的骨头
That's impossible. It'sabcthe hardest bone in the body.
而且还是躺在床上断的
And he broke it lying in bed.
连个瘀伤都没有 怎么会大腿骨折的?
How can you have a broken femurabcwithout so much as a bruise?
应该是体内因素造成的
Whatever broke it hadabcto do it from within.
成骨不全?
Osteogenesis imperfecta?
易碎的骨头不会导致打嗝abc更何况 并没有异常巩膜色变的症状
Brittle bones wouldn't cause hiccups,plus,we'd have seen abnormal coloring in the sclerae.
那就是癌了
Which leaves cancer.
啥时候开始骨癌也导致打嗝了?
Since when does boneabccancer cause hiccups?
说明不是骨癌
Which means it's not bone cancer.
或许就不是癌
Or it's not cancer.
House说得对
House is right.
即使在切尔罗贝利 都很难找到abc比这病人受到污染辐射更多的人
It'd be hard to find a guy outside chernobylabcwho'd been exposed to more carcinogens.
致癌原 杀虫剂工厂 核废料等
Pesticide plants,nuclear waste sites.
让Chase续骨 你俩准备化疗
Tell chaseto repair the break.abcYou two prep him for chemo.
你要他因为没确诊的癌而化疗?
You wanna blast him with chemo forabca cancer we don't even know he has?
不 我因癌能解释其症状而化疗
Nope,I wanna blast him with chemo forabca cancer that explains the symptoms.
髓内钉
Intramedullary nail.
等下
Hold on.
你在模仿House? 迟来的"问候"?
That your house imitation?abcSome late-breaking epiphany?
我只想你在嵌钉之前取块骨组织活检
I just need you to get a boneabcbiopsy before you insert the pin.
就为骨折?
For a broken leg?
House让他做化疗
House is prepping him for chemo.
我想给他灌毒之前值得先检查下
Thought it might be worth checking forabccancer before pumping him full of poison.
Cameron同意House的观点?
Does cameron agree with house?
Cameron不跟进这病例了
Cameron isn't on the case anymore.
你还在享受休假
Still enjoying your day off,I see.
为何让他做化疗?
Why are you prepping him for chemo?
更有趣的问题是 你为何在意?
The more interesting questionabcis why do you care?
- 你甚至不确定--abc- 我是说 你为何留要在这儿?
- You're not even sure that it's-- -abcWhat I mean is,why do you care from here?
你完全可以在家关注病人进展abc这儿和家里有什么区别?
You can monitor the patient from home.abcWhat's the difference between here and home?
你又不是我家人? 这和--
You're not at my home?Thisabchas nothing to do with--
还有什么区别吗?
Any other differences?
少医学器材 多运动胸罩abc还有蔬菜酱三明治
less medical equipment,more trainingabcbras,and more vegemite sandwiches.
实际上 现在Chase也在医院
Actually,technically,rightabcnow,chase is here.
是我叫他来的 你不知道
But that's because I calledabchim,and you didn know that.
和我的观点不相干...我推测
And it's irrelevant toabcmy point,which is...
你和Chase玩完了
you and chase are over.
你错了
You are wrong.
你认为他的衣服占一个抽屉都多了
You decided that his single drawerabcof clothes is one drawer too many.
但你没勇气告诉他...
But you don't have theabcguts to tell him,so...
所以你从感情上疏远他...
you're emotionally walking away...
而不愿正式提分手
instead of actually walking away.
真蠢 因为这样你未必会好受
Which is stupid,because only oneabcof those is good for your heart.
他准备求婚
HE's gonna ask me to marry him.
我...在找厚袜子时 找到了戒指
I... was looking for someabcthick socks. Found the ring.
你想拒绝?
And you want to say no?
那绕一大圈 又回到一抽屉衣服上--
So I circle right back toabchis single drawer of clothes--
我不知道怎么回答 我不想他求婚
I don't want to say anything.abcI don't want him to ask.
至少现在
Not now.
伤痛得不行 我们都不知所措
Couldn't hurt... we'reabcall a little freaked out.
回家 只想有人拥抱
We go home,we just wanna hug someone.
只想知道一切会正常的
We just wanna knowabceverything's gonna be okay.
我不想他因为害怕而求婚
I don't want him toabcpropose just 'cause he's scared.
她头痛 发烧 精疲力竭
She's got a headache,fever.abcShe's completely exhausted.
给他说说胸的事 亲爱的
Tell him about your chest,honey.
她的胸部很痛
Her breasts are really tender.
- 你俩一块儿热浴?abc- 没
- You guys have a hot tub?abc- No.
- 那就是去健身房了abc- 几年没去过了
- She must go to the gym a lot.abc- Not in years.
也可能 在出差的时候abc宾馆里附赠的SPA让你心动--
Then maybe,when you travel on business,youabczip on down to that complimentary hotel spa--
- 没有abc- 抱歉 你刚是说有?
- No.abc- Sorry,did you just say yes?
她到底怎么了?
What the hell's wrong with her?
- 有空吗?abc- 没空 她到底怎么了?
- Got a minute?abc- He doesn't. What's wrong with her?
抱歉 我想她那边有紧急情况
Sorry.I'm sure she'sabcgot a medical crisis,
我还需要时间想想怎么诱导你老婆回答
and I need more time to figure outabcsome leading questions for your wife.
Cameron是怎么回事?
What's going on with cameron?
她没准备回我的小组 也没准备扑向我
She doesn't want back on my teamabcand she doesn't want to jump me.
- 好吧abc- 什么?
- Okay.abc- What?
你提问题 我划掉了两种可能 你还满意?
You ask a question,I rule out twoabcpossibilities,and you're satisfied?
就是说你不想要答案
That means you don't want an answer.
你只想确认不是哪个答案
You just wanted to knowabcthere wasn't a particular answer.
要么你是担心她回到我的小组
Eith you were worried thatabcshe wanted back on my team,
要么是担心她回头找我
or you were worried thatabcshe wanted back on me.
这不是紧急情况 是不是?
This isn't a medical crisis,is it?
算是 有太多种性病 我无法确定
Could be. A lot ofabcstds hang in the balance.
我投降 用醋敷患处 每天四次
I give up. Vinegarabccompresses four times a day.
说到足够了吧?
Any chance I could just leave it at that?
才不 假球菌毛囊炎
No. Pseudomomas folliculitis.
是一种可因不洁的多人热浴abc而传染的皮肤病
It's a skin infection fromabccrowded and contaminated hot tubs,
你肯定有泡过 不过不是和你丈夫
which you obviously use,butabcnot with your husband.
我努力想帮你遮掩来着
Tried to help a sister out.
细胞核形态均正常
The nuclei were all normal sized.
骨细胞易辨认
Bone cells were well differentiated.
无异常结构证明不是癌
No dysplasia means no cancer.
- 这是好事 是吗?abc- 希望如此
- That's good,isn't it?abc- We hope so.
也意味着我们依旧不知道abc是什么导致骨折
Although it also means we stillabchave no idea what caused the break.
- 感觉如何?abc- 很痛
- How does it feel?abc- It hurts.
应该这样?
Is it supposed to look like that?
不 可能是术后出血
No,but it's probably just residualabcbleeding from the surgery.
应该可以...
We should be able to...
我要两单位新鲜冰冻血浆 马上!
I need two units of ffp,right away!
- 噢天啊! 怎么了?abc- 他在出血
- Oh,my god! What's happening?abc- He's bleeding out.
只能是癌了
Means it's gotta be cancer.
可能 但事实不是 活检阴性
It's gotta be,except it'sabcnot. The biopsy was negative.
活检可能错 症状不会
Biopsies can be wrong. Symptoms can't.
都指向癌症 但找不到就不能用放疗
All signs point to cancer,but youabccan't blast a cancer you can't find.
当然能 让他准备全身放疗
Sure you can. Prep himabcfor total body irradiation.
你知道这是疯子才干的
You do realize that's insane.
除非你认为癌聪明地藏在他体外
Not unlessyou think the cancer'sabccleverly hiding outside his body.
类固醇已经弱化了他的免疫系统
Steroids already weakenedabchis immune system.
大剂量放射在杀死癌细胞前会先杀死他
That much radiation'll killabchim before it kills the cancer.
如果没有 也很可能被我们制造出来
And if he doesn'tabchave cancer,we could cause one,
或是一并摧毁他的免疫系统
or destroy his immune system altogether.
这人可能因脚趾甲受感染而死
The guy could die fromabcan infected toe nail.
那就什么都不做 让他死了?
Y'd rather do nhing,justabclet him die on his own?
我则情愿让癌症恶化
I'd rather make his cancer worse.
用胰岛素样生长因子 促肿瘤生长
Give him insulin-like growthabcfactor,make any tumor or malignancy grow.
长大到我们能发现为止
Grows big enough,we can find it.
这是火上浇油
That's like pouring gasoline on a fire.
至少全身放疗还算是治疗
At least total body irradiation'sabcan actual treatment.
他的主意更好 去干吧
His idea is better. Pour away.
我的法力掉了
I lost my mojo.
你倒回去找了吗?
Have you retraced your steps?
清洁工在洗衣服前掏过口袋了吗--
Does your cleaning lady checkabcyour pockets before--
我弄不清Kutner寻死的原因abc对Cameron也猜测错了
I was clueless about kutner.abcI was wrong about cameron.
Taub刚说的主意 我早该先想到的
Taub just came up with an idea thatabcI should have seen long before he did.
Kutner的事没人能预料
No one saw anything coming with kutner.
你也不常见到Cameron
You hardly ever see cameron anymore.
你雇Taub的目的就是让他abc在你没主意时突发奇想
And you hired taub to come up with ideasabcthat you wouldn't have come up with.
我不知道你为何吃胡萝卜
And I have no ideawhyabcyou're eating carrots.
好啊
Good.
我脑子坏了 你却说"好"?
I'm losing my mind. Allabcyou got to say is "good"?
House 一个受你指导 与你共事两年
House,a guy you worked with forabctwo years,who you mentored
或许还是你关心的人 突然扣扳机自杀了
and,yes,possibly even caredabcabout,just blew his brains out.
你找不到原因 找不到意义abc有时候其实根本就没有
You can't find the reason,can't find theabcmeaning in it,because sometimes there isn't any.
有时候...事情就这样了
Sometimes... this is all there is.
你是该失落
You should be losing it.
这种境况下 你还神采飞扬才不正常
You'd be crazy not to be off your game.
法力就在你失落它的地方
But your mojo is right where you left it.
只要... 继续玩下去 我走了
Just... keep playingabcwith it. I gotta go.
要吃自己拿
Help yourself.
我知道这是痛苦的过程
I know this is a tough process.
一发现有肿块或者肿瘤...
At the first sign of anyabctumors or masses,we can...
就祈祷上帝保佑?
Tart saying prayers?
没事的 一旦--
It's gonna beabcokay.Once we can--
不 一点都不好 你这是在让癌生长
No,it's not gonna be okay.abcYou're growing his cancer.
这不是医生的错
This isn't the doctors' fault.
我自愿暴露在糟糕的环境中
I've exposed myself toabca lot of bad stuff.
我知道风险
I knew the risks.
我想要人生有意义
I want my life to mean something.
如果这意味着我一定要...
If that means I'm destined to...
室性心动过速 无脉搏!abc准备抢救!
He's in v-tach and noabcpulse! Grab the paddles!
噢 天啊!
Oh,god!
充电 让开!
Charging. Clear!
充电 让开
Charging. Clear.
我在找你
I've been looking for you.
我... 我一直在想你
And... I've been thinking about you.
只是还没开始找
Just hadn't reached theabclooking stage yet.
问题就在这儿
Which is the problem.
你要一天 我给了俩
You asked for a day. I gave you two.
你说有个不能分享的秘密 我尊重了
You told me you had a secret youabccouldn't share. I respected that.
现在我不知道还会不会有更糟糕的--abc放弃假期来陪House转
Now I don't know what's worse-- blowingabcoff our vacation to hang around house
或是因为House不陪你而继续放弃假期
or continuing to blow itabcoff when he won't hang around you.
如果你认为我还对House有意--
If you think I'm theabcleast bit interested in house--
我不知道该怎么想
I don't know what I'm supposed to think.
我知道这看起来很糟--
I know thisabclooks bad,and--
我不在乎看起来如何 我在乎本质
I don't care how itabclooks.I care what it is.
你没告诉我本质
And you're not telling me what it is.
我想相信你 但...
I'm trying to trust you,but...
只是...
Just...
我还要点时间
I need a little more time.
不
No.
这...和House无关
This... has nothing to do with house.
也和我无关了 再也不会了
Yeah,well,it has nothing to doabcwith me,either. Not anymore.
方便时叫我来收拾东西
Let me know when I canabccome pick up my things.
超声心动图没显示任何东西abc测了肌钙蛋白  没有心肌缺血的表现
Nothing on the echo. We drew a troponinabclevel. No signs of myocardial ischemia.
所有检查都显示正常
All e tests were normal.
失去平衡 病理性打嗝 肺漏气
Loss of balance. Pathologicalabchiccups. Air leak between the lungs.
腿骨骨折 现在又心动过速 继续!
Broken femur,now tachycardia. Go!
说啊 说点什么 坏主意都行
Come on,give me something.abcGive me a bad idea.
或许我能改好它
Maybe I could turn it into a good one.
好吧 把他切开 装个除颤器
Fine. Open him up,putabcin a defibrillator.
这是永久的而且很危险
That's permanent and risky.
我们都不知道他的心脏是否有问题
We don't even know what,ifabcanything,is wrong with his heart.
重做检查 与此同时 切开他 装除颤器...
Redo all the tests. In the meantime,openabchim up,put in a defibrillator...
这样他能撑到你做完检查
so he can live long enough forabcyou to finish the tests.
平衡 器官 神经 肺 骨 心脏
Balance organs,nerves,lungs,bones,heart.
像是德式小香肠的原料
Things you use to make bratwurst.
没有感染迹象
There's no sign of infection.
也不是代谢性或自身免疫疾病
It's not a metabolic orabcautoimmune disease.
肯定也不是癌症 我认为
It's definitely not cancer. I think.
肯定不是癌症
Definitely not cancer.
你不选吗?
Aren't you gonna pick?
我在思考 难道这还要计时?
I'm thinking. Is there a ticking clock?
你已经把你的钱放进去了
You already put your money in.
你绝不会在决定好之前这么做
You never do that until you decide.
你真是观察入微 可惜你打扰到我了
That's very observant of you.abcToo bad you distracted me.
现在我...也许改变主意了
Now I'M... thinkingabcI might change my mind.
那机器里没有什么健康食物
There's nothing healthy in that machine.
不 里面没有
No,there's not.
古米熊 你讨厌古米熊的
Gummi bears. You hate gummi bears.
- 人是会变的abc- 不会
- People can change.abc- No.
更重要的是 我不喜欢
More importantly,I hate them.
喔好...那我不请你吃了
Oh,fine... then I won't offer you any.
你个诡计多端的小人
You manipulative bitch.
你不是因为想要吃健康食物而吃
You're not suddenlyabceating healthy because you want to.
你吃这些是因为你知道我不愿意吃
You're eating healthyabcbecause you know I don't want to.
这十年来 我都顺走你的食物
I've been mooching food for ten years.
现在 要么是这周起 你突然间要奋起反抗
Now,either it suddenlyabcstarted bothering you this week
- 或者你是在...abc- 和你捣乱
- or you're-- -abcScrewing with you.
总有人要这么做的
It needed to be done.
自从Amber死了 我退缩 试图改变一切
After amber died,I withdrew,triedabcto change everything,
希望我能探寻到一些深奥的真理
hoping I'd sort itabcout,find some deeper truth.
这是一个错误
It was a mistake.
我应该回复正常的生活abc回到这里 回到现实中
I should have gone back toabcnormal,to here and now,
因为这是我们唯一能倚靠的
because that's all weabccan ever really count on.
每一件事都需要回归常态 那么...
Things need to get back toabcnormal in your life,and...
有什么能比我和你添乱更自然而然的呢?
what could be more normal thanabcme screwing with you...
你这不是戳穿我了?
and you figuring it out?
你个诡计多端的小人
You manipulative bitch.
我们需要植入一个心脏复律除颤器
We need to put in aabccardioverter-defibrillator.
这会在我们查找病因时abc保证心脏维持跳动
It'll keep your heartabcbeating while we keep looking.
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
意思是 即使我们找到了病因
It means,even if we figure this out,
你以后都不能在任何abc远离医院的地方举行抗议
you'll have to stopabcprotesting anywhere not near a hospital.
有一些问题
Got a few questions.
呃 正要开始...
Uh,we're about toabcstart doing--
一个毫无意义的医疗手术
A hopefully pointless medical procedure.
你的命和我的法力悬而未决
Your life and myabcmojo hang in the balance.
杀虫剂是有害的
Pesticides are evil.
意味着商品花卉abc都在有害的水源中汲取水分
Which means that commercial flowersabcare dowsed in evil.
但植物的生命是大自然abc对有害事物的回答
But plant life isabcnature's answer to evil.
你有花园吗?
So you have a garden?
不 我们住在公寓里
No,we live in an apartment.
- 窗台上有没有花盆箱?abc- 没有
- A window box,then?abc- No.
- 盆栽呢?abc- 什么都没有 商品花卉都是--
- Potted plants? - Nothing,theabccommercial growers--
它们有害 对 我知道了
Yeah,they're evil. Yeah,got it.
House 真的没时间说这些
House,I really don't think weabchave the time for this.
你的婚姻糟透了
Your marriage sucks.
谢谢
Thank you.
所有的婚姻都很糟糕 你们的也是
All marriages suck. Your marriage sucks.
- 不abc- 我爱她
- No.abc- I love her.
他爱俄勒冈州的树都比爱你的多
He loves a tree inabcoregon more than he loves you.
但他不能和树上床
But he can't have sex with it.
除非是波特兰那棵淫荡的橡树
Unless it's that sluttyabcoak outside rtland.
你想要说明什么?
You wanna get to your point?
她受够了 她会离开的
She's had enough. She's gonna leave.
或者她不愿迎合你了 诸如此类
Or maybe she's justabcnot putting out,whatever.
你要补救这一切 晚了就来不及
You gotta make it right,right away.
你打破了那条抵抗市售鲜花的原则
You gotta compromiseabcthat precious flower principle.
从来没有过
Never.
就一次
Once.
三周前 我们的结婚纪念日
Three weeks ago. Our anniversary.
我为了在那个集会 错过了晚餐
I missed the dinner to be at that rally.
你计划了几个月abc你很生气 真的很生气
You planned it for months.abcYou were mad. Really mad.
我给你买了花 我把花带回家
I bought you flowers.abcI brought them home.
但是你不见了 行李箱也带走了
And you were gone. So was your suitcase.
我扔了它们 给你买了耳环
I tossed them andabcbought you the earrings.
玫瑰?
Roses?
对了 你得了孢子丝菌病
Yes. You have sporotrichosis.
这由玫瑰刺导致的感染abc玫瑰 又叫做便宜的婚姻拯救品
It's an infection from the thorn of the roseabcwhich,by any other name,is still a cheap marital aid.
是花让我...
The flowers are what gave me--
第八根颅神经上的损伤破坏了你的平衡
Lesion on your eight hcranialabcnerve knocks out your balance.
膈神经上的另一处损伤导致了连续打嗝
Another on your phrenicabcnerve gives you serial hiccups.
我们用的类固醇和胰岛素样生长因子abc使感染扩散到了骨骼和心脏
We then spread it to your bones and heartabcwith steroids and insulin-like growth factor.
请告诉我们这是个好消息
Please tell us that this is good news.
对他来说是好消息
It's good news for him.
对人类下一代来说是好消息
It's good news for future generations.
对你来说是个坏消息 他会好起来
It's crappy news forabcyou. He's gonna be fine.
他再也不会自我怀疑
He'll never doubt himself again.
好了
There you go.
该死 我还希望能打断些什么
Damn,I was hoping Iabcwould interrupt something.
你欠的情还了 病人已经治好了
Your favor's repaid. Patient's cured.
他已经在为下周另一个abc地球清洁日的集会收拾行李了
He's already packing for anotherabcearth day extravaganza next week.
他差点死了 他就不能在家陪家人几天?
He almost died. He can't take aabcfew days at home with his family?
人在创伤之后若是改变了abc只因为在受伤之前就已经有此打算
People only change after trauma ifabcthey wanted to change before the trauma.
又或者是他们看了太多课外电视节目
Or if they've watched tooabcmany afterschool specials.
- 你在说Chase?abc- 我在说你
- You talking about chase?abc- I'm talking about you.
你失去了第一个丈夫
You lost husband number one.
同事的死让你质疑一段长期关系abc一点都不奇怪
No surprise that the death of a colleagueabcwould make you question another long-term lease.
你还教授婚恋课程?abc我以为你光说教就已经太忙...
You teaching commitment classes? 'Cause Iabcthought you were too busy with your lecture--
我知道你反应会很激烈
I'm sure that was going to be hysterical.
让我告诉你重点
Let me just give you the cliff notes.
别试图通过给我病例而甩了他
Don't try to dump him byabcdumping cases on me.
我说过 我从没想过甩了Chase
I told you I never wanted to dump chase.
当然 你希望他甩了你
Bsolutely. You want him to dump you.
这完全不同 罪恶感少多了
It's totally different. Much less guilt.
不管如何 你都没有避开他的理由了
Either way,you're out ofabcreasons to avoid him.
把Kutner当作借口很拙劣
Kutner was a prettyabcdumb one to begin with.
我不该推迟假期的
I should neverabchave postponed our vacation.
我就不该计划
I should never have planned it.
我在袜子里找到了戒指
I found the ring in your sock.
我不希望你是...
I didn't want you toabcpropose out of some sort of...
对Kutner的死如膝跳反应般 向我求婚
knee-jerk reaction toabcwhat happened to kutner.
那么 我猜你不用再担心了
Well,guess you don't have toabcworry about that anymore.
我不是 我...
I'm not,I...
我不在乎发生了什么abc我只是...希望能发生
I don't care what happens.abcI just... want it to happen.
你...你是不是在向我求婚?
Are--areabcyou proposing to me?
我 我是在建议...
I'M... proposing that...
你向我求婚
you propose to me.
在我和你分手之后?
After I broke up with you?
在你毁了我计划好的求婚之后abc你期望我...
After you ruined my plannedabcproposal,you expect me to--
我不是期望 我是希望
I'm not expecting. I'm hoping.
好的
Yes.
解决了另一个病例
Solved another case.
Wilson真差劲
Busted wilson.
看来你根本没有迷失
Looks like you'reabcnot losing it after all.